3balls.com 2016-10-21

# Help Desk | 3balls.com

**3balls.com, Inc. Internet Privacy Policy**

The Privacy Policy below describes the information that is collected from users on the website, www.3balls.com (hereinafter “site” or “Site”) and what we do with the information collected. If you have any questions or comments about the Privacy Policy, feel free to contact us at customerservice@3balls.com. This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that 3balls.com does not own or control, or to people that 3balls.com does not employ or manage.

**Collected Information**

At 3balls.com, you may be ordering products, contacting us or subscribing to our online newsletters. Most of the personal information that we collect is required in order to properly fulfill your order. Some of the information you may be asked to submit include the following: name, shipping address, billing address, e-mail address, telephone number, credit card information, gender, age, birth date, income level, etc.

Certain features of our site may only be available to customers who provide us with the requested information such as those that are ordering products. 

3balls.com may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit our website such as: the referring domain before visiting our website, the path analysis of the customer on our website, the type of browser you are using and the domain name of your Internet service provider. The information we collect may also include information you submit about others, including the name, e-mail address or physical address of a gift recipient. We only use information you submit about other people to deliver information, products, or services specifically requested by you or to cooperate with law enforcement officials in the investigation of alleged unlawful activities of our customers. 

Subject to the other terms of our Privacy Policy, we may aggregate (i.e. assemble on a basis that does not enable one to personally identify you) the data that is acquired under or in connection with this site and/or related to ordering our products and services, including, without limitation, data about the products and services requested and purchased by our Users. Aggregated data may be used by us to improve our Services and for marketing purposes, and may be shared with and used by advertisers and other third parties. We may also use such data to determine what types of services are best suited for our customers and what types of services our customers request. If we provide aggregated data to third parties, particular personal information (including birth date, name, title, income level, home address, dependent information and any other identifying information) will not be individually identifiable in the aggregated data.

Notwithstanding anything in this privacy policy to the contrary, 3balls.com has contracted with third parties to provide tracking and analysis of information and data collected from visitors to our website. 3balls.com reserves the right to provide that information and data to such third parties for those purposes. Such information and data is provided on a basis that does not enable a third party to identify you.

Your use the services provided by 3balls.com constitutes your consent to the use of such data on an aggregated basis.

**The Use of Information**

3balls.com may provide certain demographic information it collects to third parties in connection with its provision of Services to our Users. The dissemination of this information is necessary in order to provide personalized information and promotional offers. Except as disclosed in this Privacy Policy, our current policy is to refrain from selling, leasing, or otherwise transferring your personally identifiable information, however, this policy does not apply in all cases and this policy may be changed in the future. We describe below some of the situations in which such information may be disclosed. 3balls.com will never provide our promotional affiliates with personally identifiable information which would permit them to communicate with our Users by email unless the User "opts-in" and have not "opted-out", pursuant to our opt-out procedure, from receiving communications. You may have the opportunity to ask us to provide your information to these promotional affiliates. We expect those promotional partners with whom we share information (with consent, as provided herein) to respect the privacy of our Users in the same manner as we do. However, we cannot ensure that they abide by our privacy policies. 

The information you provide about yourself is used to provide the products and services that you have requested or what we think you might be interested in. The information we collect may also be used to contact you due to problems with your request or to update you about new products and customer promotions.

3balls.com will use the non-personally identifiable aggregate information that we collect to assess your satisfaction with and to improve the design and content of our website We may use the contact information we collect to provide, by means other than email, information or offers which we believe will be of value to Users and we may share contact information with other companies that may want to provide our Users, by means other than email, information regarding additional products and services. We may also use the contact information to send our Users information or offers by email which we believe will be of value to them and we may share email contact information with other companies that may want to provide our Users information regarding additional products and services. Such contact information may be shared based upon the demographic information we collect. Users may opt-out of receiving future communications at any time; see the section below regarding "Opt-out". 

Employees of 3balls.com and its affiliates who have access to personally identifiable information are obligated to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. The personal information will only be used to carry out the orders/services they are providing you from 3balls.com.

**Disclosure for Legal Purposes**  

Given the government's current interest in Internet regulation, you hereby authorize us to disclose information pursuant to judicial and administrative proceedings, and in connection with law enforcement activities and as otherwise may be permitted by law, to law enforcement or government agencies if we believe the disclosure is necessary or appropriate. You also authorize us to disclose information if we believe the disclosure is necessary or appropriate in the event of an investigation of improper or illegal conduct in connection with our Web site, such as fraud, misrepresentation, intellectual-property infringement, or other activity that may put us at risk for liability. We will, whenever we believe reasonably possible, use our reasonable efforts to inform a User whose information may be so revealed.

**Other Use**

It is possible that 3balls.com, its business and/or assets, its present or future subsidiaries, joint ventures or any combination of such, could merge with or be acquired in one or more types of transactions by another business entity or entities. Should such transaction(s) occur, 3balls.com has your permission to share some or all of your information in order to, among other things, continuation of one or more services similar to all or a portion of the services that 3balls.com currently provides. We will require that the new combined entity adhere to the practices disclosed in this Privacy Policy.

**Cookies**

Like many companies, we use "cookies" on our website. Cookies are information files that your web browser places on the hard drive of your computer when you visit a website. Cookies cannot damage user files, nor can they read information from a user's hard drive. Cookies allow websites to remember user's activities on a website. Cookies help us recognize repeat visitors, allowing communication of a personalized welcome message and tailoring of content to match particular interests. For example, cookies may be used to remember what is in your shopping cart after leaving the website. You can disable cookies on your computer by indicating this in the preferences or options menus in your browser. 

We also may use outside advertising companies to display advertisements on our site. These advertisements may also contain cookies. Some customer data may be shared with the advertising affiliates on an aggregated basis in accordance with the other terms of this Privacy Policy. Because cookies are stored on your hard drive, not on our Web site, you are always free to set your browser to decline cookies and you can delete them from your computer. If you decline "cookies" or delete them from your computer, you will still be able to access our Web site, but you may find that some areas do not work as smoothly as when cookies are enabled on your system.

We do not link data collected from cookies to your personally identifiable information.

**IP Addresses**

Like many companies, we automatically track certain information based on your behavior on our website. 3balls.com might use the information collected to do research on our customers’ website behavior as well as demographics. The information we collect might include the URL where you came from and the pages you go to next. We also might collect information on your IP address (Internet Protocol). An ISP provides a unique IP address every time if you are using a dial up. However for LAN or cable models, an IP address may be permanently assigned to one computer. IP addresses are automatically logged by web servers, collecting information about a user's traffic patterns. An IP address does not identify an individual by name; however it can reveal what geographic area you are connecting from. 

**Confidentiality and Security**

3balls.com is committed to making your online ordering process secure.  We have implemented security safeguards designed to protect the personal information that you provide when logging into your user account, in accordance with industry standards. Access to your personally identifiable data from your user account such as credit card information is protected by SSL encryption when it is exchanged between your web browser and the site. However, since the Internet is not a 100% secure environment, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you transmit to us. There is no guarantee that information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. It is your responsibility to protect the security of your login information. 

Be sure to log off from 3balls.com when finished using a shared computer. No administrator at 3balls.com will have knowledge of your password. 3balls.com also protects your personal information off-line. Access to your personal information is limited to employees who 3balls.com reasonably believes will need that information to provide services to you. However, 3balls.com is not responsible for the confidentiality, security or distribution of your own personal information by our partners and third parties outside the scope of our agreement with such partners and third parties. 

**Children's and Minor's Privacy**

This site is, generally, directed at persons over the age of 13 who purchase items with credit cards and we do not knowingly collect personal information from or about children under the age of 13 except as relating to a specific order for products or services. If we, at any time, learn that information relating to a child under the age of 13 that we have obtained is other than as set forth above, we shall immediately purge such information from our records.

3balls.com strongly encourages parents and guardians to supervise the online activities of their minor children and consider using parental control tools available from online services and software manufacturers to help provide a child-friendly online environment. These tools also can prevent minors from disclosing their name, address, and other personally identifiable information online without parental permission. 

**Links**

The site, [www.3balls.com](https://www.3balls.com/) may contain links to other sites. The linked sites are not necessarily under the control of 3balls.com. Please be aware that 3balls.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. 3balls.com encourages you to be aware when you leave this site and to read the privacy policies of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. If you decide to access any of the third-party sites linked to this site, you do this entirely at your own risk. Any links to any partner of the site should be the responsibility of the linking party, and 3balls.com shall not be responsible for notification of any change in name or location of any information on the site. 

**Surveys, Contests, Special Offers**

From time to time, 3balls.com may provide persons over the age of [13] with the opportunity to participate in surveys, contests, or special offers on our site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. The requested information typically includes contact information such as name and shipping address. We use this information to notify contest winners and award prizes, and to send participants an email alert, if they choose to receive it. 

Participation in these surveys, contests, or special offers is completely voluntary.   
We may have other similar offers or programs on our site and unless we indicate otherwise at the time that we collect the information, we will use such information in accordance with our Privacy Policy. 

**California Residents**

California Civil Code Section 1798.83, known as the “Shine The Light” law, permits our customers who are California residents to request and obtain from us a list of what personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year and the names and addresses of those third parties. Requests may be made only once a year and are free of charge. Under Section 1798.83, we currently do not share any personal information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes.

**How You Can Modify Information, Opt Out, or Contact Us**

You can review and modify (or remove) the information you provide us in the order or registration process if this information changes. The information that you may change (or remove) includes any information provided on our order or registration format. To make any of these changes, you may log on to this site and make the changes directly after you have received an identification and password for the transaction or for the individual order.

After either completing your first purchase at 3balls.com or otherwise using our registration module, your registration on our Web site will be confirmed by an email correspondence to your email address. If you do not object to such email within three days, it will constitute your consent to receive email notices and other email communications from 3balls.com and its advertisers and promotional affiliates. In the event you no longer wish to receive such email notices or other email communications from us, you may opt-out by removing yourself through our opt-out procedures. You may also contact us at customerservice@3balls.com if you no longer wish to be enrolled as a User.

**Updates to Privacy Policy**

The 3balls.com Privacy Policy was last updated in February 2016. We encourage you to periodically check our Privacy Policy and review so you always understand what information we are collecting from you. For any questions about our Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us at customerservice@3balls.com. 

Was this answer helpful? YesNo

Send
